import React from "react";

const questions = [
  {
    question: "What is the only real activity of the Absolute Observer?",
    options: ["Dreaming", "Doing", "Observing", "Witnessing"],
    answer: "Observing",
  },
  {
    question: "What happens to You in deep sleep?",
    options: [
      "You forget yourself",
      "You disappear",
      "Conscious presence disappears",
      "You become unconscious",
    ],
    answer: "Conscious presence disappears",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the true nature of all forms in space?",
    options: [
      "Real manifestations",
      "Independent realities",
      "Reflections only",
      "Metaphors of life",
    ],
    answer: "Reflections only",
  },
  {
    question: "What is your relationship to Consciousness?",
    options: [
      "You are created by it",
      "You are its function",
      "You are prior to it",
      "You are one with it",
    ],
    answer: "You are prior to it",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the highest use of the form?",
    options: [
      "To achieve something",
      "To experience joy",
      "To know your ‘I Am-ness’",
      "To serve others",
    ],
    answer: "To know your ‘I Am-ness’",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the nature of Stillness?",
    options: [
      "The final goal",
      "An object to be attained",
      "The seed of Consciousness",
      "The state of the Witness",
    ],
    answer: "The seed of Consciousness",
  },
  {
    question: "What happens in space?",
    options: [
      "Divine play",
      "Everything real",
      "Nothing but reflected show in Consciousness just now",
      "Birth and death",
    ],
    answer: "Nothing but reflected show in Consciousness just now",
  },
  {
    question: "How is Love known?",
    options: [
      "Through another",
      "Through words",
      "When Consciousness is Conscious of itself",
      "When you feel it",
    ],
    answer: "When Consciousness is Conscious of itself",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the meaning of “Nothing never happens to you”?",
    options: [
      "Everything happens for a reason",
      "Only good happens to you",
      "You are unaffected by all",
      "You must accept suffering",
    ],
    answer: "You are unaffected by all",
  },
  {
    question: "Who are you Just Now?",
    options: [
      "A person on a path",
      "A seeker of the Truth",
      "The Consciousness dreaming this world",
      "The Absolute Observer, Eternal, Unborn",
    ],
    answer: "The Absolute Observer, Eternal, Unborn",
  },
];

export default questions;
